Contact

youssefabukhalifa@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/youssef-abukhalifa-08170b269 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Back-End Web Development
Data Analysis
Scientific Research

Languages

Arabic English

Certifications

3rd software category
Php

Soft skills

Scientific Research

DECI Geeks

Youssef Abukhalifa

Scientific Researcher | 3rd software Basef | Basef finalist 3 times | Back end developer | Software Developer |DECI Initiative L3 | Junior Data analyst

Damietta, Dumyat, Egypt

Summary

I am a skilled programmer with expertise in HTML, CSS, PHP, Laravel, XAMPP, MySQL, and Python data analysis. I also have knowledge of UI/UX design, AI, and MI. I am in the DECI initiative, powered by udacity. I have a strong background in scientific research, having placed third in the SOFT category at the BASEF competition in 2023. Finalist 3 times in BASEF. I am also a certificate holder from the Horus University Innovation Camp.

Experience

The Earth Care Solutions
Web Developer
March 2024 - Present (1 month)
Egypt

Digital Egypt Cubs Initiative "DECI" DECI L3 Data&Ai January 2024 - Present (3 months)

Freelance
Back End Developer
May 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Egypt

Society for Science Scientific Researcher October 2020 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Can to be team
Video Editing
April 2023 - Present (1 year)

Researchers Team

Member of academic committee

January 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Digital Egypt Cubs Initiative "DECI" Deci level 2 November 2022 - August 2023 (10 months)

Education

Udacity

Information Technology Institute (ITI)

Udemy